{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which Indian fruit contains all kinds of vitamins?",
      "no_of_answers": 3,
      "last_followed": "1h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which country is famous for hockey?",
      "no_of_answers": 0,
      "last_followed": "15m",
      "followed_by": 2,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What is the scope of machine learning in the future?",
      "no_of_answers": 43,
      "last_followed": " Oct 11",
      "followed_by": 52,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which keto diet is the best? Is Keto diet really helpful?",
      "no_of_answers": 4,
      "last_followed": "Dec 31",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What happens if you don't update your Android smartphone?",
      "no_of_answers": 1,
      "last_followed": "2h",
      "followed_by": 0,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What is Google, and who made it?",
      "no_of_answers": 0,
      "last_followed": "1h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What are the benefits of playing pickle ball over tennis?",
      "no_of_answers": 2,
      "last_followed": "5h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Why do people not ask questions before they or their family get impacted?",
      "no_of_answers": 2,
      "last_followed": "5h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which is the best platform for earning money online in 2023, YouTube or Quora?",
      "no_of_answers": 1,
      "last_followed": "2h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What are the benefits of yoga at home?",
      "no_of_answers": 0,
      "last_followed": "2h",
      "followed_by": 1,
      "answers": []
    }
  ]
}
